UNITE Southern Regional Joint Board Records 6000/045
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Southern Regional Joint Board Records
1997-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Southern Regional Joint Board
6000/045
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Files, records.
6766713
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles., October 30, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Clothing industry--New York (State)--New York; Clothing industry--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile industry--United States.; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--United States.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Constitutions.
6766713
- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Prize Award Program., 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UNITE. Constitution. English., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UNITE. Constitution. French., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UNITE. Constitution. Spanish., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- UNITE. Directory of Products Made by Our Members., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UNITE. General Executive Board. Meeting Materials., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- UNITE. Proceedings of the 2nd Convention. Vol. 1., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE. Proceedings of the 2nd Convention. Vol. 2., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UNITE. Proceedings of the 2nd Convention. Vol. 3., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- UNITE. Shops by State and Congressional District., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UNITE. Shops by State and Congressional District., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)